A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, International Division, Asia and Pacific, Program Area One Files FA554
Rockefeller Archive Center
- China, II
  - International Training and Research (ITR) -- China, Hongkong General Correspondence, 1957-1959 (Box 2)
  - International Training and Research (ITR) -- China, Hongkong General Correspondence, 1960-1961 (Box 2)
  - International Training and Research (ITR) -- China, Hongkong General Correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - International Training and Research (ITR) in the Ford Foundation Report -- Swayzee, Jun 1967 (Box 2)
- Iran, III
  - Tehran Chronological File, Jul-Dec 1961 (Box 3)
  - Tehran Chronological File, Jan-Jun 1962 (Box 3)
  - Tehran Chronological File, Jul-Dec 1962 (Box 3)
  - Tehran Chronological File, 1963 (Box 3)
  - Tehran Chronological File, 1964 (Box 3)
- Pakistan, IV
  - Pakistan Planning Commission, 1960-1961 (Box 3)
  - Ford Foundation -- Pakistan, 1969-1972 (Box 3)
  - The Ford Foundation in Pakistan Information Paper, Jun 1970 (Box 3)
  - Pakistan, 1971 (Box 3)
  - Ian Martin -- Pakistan, 1971-1972 (Box 3)
  - Pakistan -- Miscellaneous Ford Foundation Memoranda, Apr 2, 1971-Mar 22, 1972 (Box 3)
  - Pakistan -- Eugene S. Staples (ESS) Report, May 25, 1971 (Box 3)
  - Pakistan -- Eugene S. Staples (ESS) Report, Jun 22, 1971 (Box 3)
  - Pakistan -- Eugene S. Staples (ESS) Report, Sep 15, 1971 (Box 3)
  - Pakistan -- Eugene S. Staples (ESS) Report, Nov 15, 1971 (Box 3)
  - Pakistan -- Eugene S. Staples (ESS) Report, Dec 10, 1971 (Box 3)
  - Pakistan -- Eugene S. Staples (ESS) Report, Mar 23, 1972 (Box 3)
  - Pakistan -- "Trustees' Wives" Speech Manuscript, Mar 28, 1972 (Box 3)
  - Wilhelm Memoranda "Situation in India", Mar 1, 1972 (Box 3)
  - "Bangladesh" Memorandum from George Zeidenstein, Mar 22, 1972 (Box 3)
  - Chron -- Pakistan -- Outlook Article, Mar 20, 1973 (Box 3)
- Herbert Passin files, V
  - Asia -- Miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 4)
  - Background -- Hong Kong, 1967 (Box 4)
  - Background Material -- Japan, 1961-1967 (Box 4)
  - Background -- Korea, 1966-1968 (Box 4)
  - Background -- Taiwan, 1967 (Box 4)
  - China -- Taiwan, 1968 (Box 4)
  - Committee for Cooperation on English in Japan (1/2), 1968 (Box 4)
  - Committee for Cooperation on English in Japan (2/2), 1968-1969 (Box 4)
  - English as a Second Language (ESL) (1/3), 1967 (Box 4)
  - English as a Second Language (ESL) (2/3), 1968 (Box 4)
  - English as a Second Language (ESL) (3/3), 1966-1969 (Box 4)
  - Hawaii, 1968 (Box 4)
  - JCCC -- Japan, 1964-1966 (Box 4)
  - Japan Program -- Lists, budgts, 1970 (Box 4)
  - Japan Review, 1966-1968 (Box 4)
  - Memoranda -- General, 1968 (Box 4)
  - Pending, 1968 (Box 4)
  - Preliminary Activities in Connection with the Teaching of English as a Second Language in Japan (OIR) PA-67-37, 1967 (Box 4)
  - Princeton -- East Asian Program, 1969 (Box 4)
  - Eugene S. Staples' Trip to Japan, 1968 (Box 4)
  - U.S. -- Japan Parliamentary Exchange 68-218, 1967-1968 (Box 4)